Hey fam, we're here at Canazowl Castle.
>> That's who says that. Hey,
>> you do.
>> I don't not say hey fam.
>> Hello world where I'm from. This is what
a trip to a historical city that is not
[music] Kyoto is like.
>> You're at the aquarium fam.
>> No.
>> So where did we go?
>> So we went to Ishikawa Kim and a place
called Kazawa City.
>> Yeah. And why did we go there? Um, well,
because you said we're going, [laughter]
>> I I had seven prefectures left that I
hadn't visited, and I gave the list to
Aiko. There was Wakayama,
>> uh, there was Ishikawa, there was
Yamaguchi,
there was Yamanashi,
Shigaken, Gefu,
uh, and there's probably one more that I
forgot, but they're not that important
since I forgot it.
>> But why did you pick Ishikawaken out of
the seven remaining prefectures? M I
guess like I always wanted to go to
Kazawa because uh the the kaisen the
seafood is like famous and I really like
seafood so I just wanted to eat.
>> That was the whole reason really.
>> Mhm.
>> Okay. Uh I was interested in going to
Kanazawa because
it's called Little Kyoto.
>> People always talk about over tourism
and that Kyoto is so crowded. So I
thought, well, let's see what the little
Kyoto is like, so maybe people could go
there instead.
>> This is from Michelin Star Chef. So it's
got this menu.
>> Oh,
>> they actually felt quite healthy and
very tasty. So I was impressed with it
actually. I would order that again.
>> This has 466 calories.
>> Yeah.
This is like egg and onions. And this is
just
>> it's like simple.
>> It wasn't that pricey though. I was
surprised.
>> Yeah, I think
>> yours was more expensive than mine. It
>> was expensive.
>> So, we left from Tokyo station and the
trick I think is you don't get your
echuban after you enter the Shinkansen
area. You get it before you enter. Cuz
when we like we went there and they just
had so many shops selling, right?
>> Yeah. There's so many. And you there's
like lots of v varieties. So, you know,
if you don't like seafood or fish, like,
you know, you can get like
>> salad based ones.
>> Yeah. Salad or meat. But once you get in
the kaisatu
>> Yeah. under that past the ticket gates.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. There's just like only limited.
And I think I I didn't see much. There
wasn't
>> They have some, but it's it's pretty
basic. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, like if you really want to
choose what you want to eat, then you
should go before
Yeah. Yeah. We need to catch the bus to
go to the hotel. It's the same one.
>> Okay. So, you can take the 94, the 92,
the 95. It doesn't matter.
>> And uh we kind of had a problem there.
>> They don't take the IC cards. Yes. So
like pass mo or seikka
>> just right before we're go to go in the
entrance it said like no I see.
>> So luckily I had a couple credit cards
on me one on my phone loaded up my phone
and one physical one so I can give my
physical card to Io to tap in. Then I
used the one on my phone.
>> We got to the hotel late so we bathed
and went to bed. The next morning we
headed out towards the castle. What do
you think this is over here?
>> I mean, is this bamboo or something?
>> I feel like that's rice straw,
>> right? From k from rice. After you
harvest it, you gather it like that,
>> I think.
>> But this this this would be bamboo.
>> I'm going to film a project next year
where they're using this to shade tea
leaves. [clears throat]
>> Oh, this is kind of like hotoesque.
>> Yeah, this looks nice. Do you remember
how to pray?
>> I don't like there's so many ways to do
it. I don't know which like is the
correct way.
>> This is Shinto. I'll show you. Here. You
can hold the camera then. I only have
Kaku. They're going to be very happy.
Traditionally, you give Goen, which is
five yen. This is 100 yen.
>> Very big donation.
>> Okay. You got to remember now.
You go.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I know now. I
know now. [snorts] Okay. But usually
like tick tick tick tick. You ready?
>> Oh, he has a bell.
>> Yeah. And then you do this
and then
>> do you know the reason for this? Uh they
have forgot.
>> I think
>> I think it's just to hide stuff and look
cool. I I don't
>> Oh, like something to do with like water
or something.
>> Looking it up, it's called yaraki or enu
yarai. While it looks decorative, it
also functions as protection from mud
and splatter for wood or plaster walls.
Additionally, it stops animals from
peeing on said walls, passerbys from
getting close to the wall, and thieves
from easily getting access to a home.
>> All the buildings
around here looks kind of like you know
castle type of
buildings.
>> Hey.
>> Mhm.
>> What is this?
>> Are we
Looks nice.
>> It looks very cold. I have experience
living in a place kind of like this.
You see this over here?
>> Mhm.
>> There's nothing underneath, right?
There's air passes right through
underneath the building. Yeah.
>> I think a lot of old Japanese buildings
are dark inside.
>> I don't know why they don't like light.
>> It looks pretty neat though.
>> A mix between Western and Japanese cuz
look at the roof.
>> This side. [laughter]
This one looks more like Japanese.
>> You're going in. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa.
>> I guess this is not safe.
>> I like the the yard.
>> The garden. the garden. I think it it
would look um cooler if there was more
snow.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> What's it say? Can you read it?
>> It's kind of I think the first one is
matsu.
>> Oh,
>> but after that I can't.
It's like
>> you've won awards for your calligraphy.
>> Well, not this type of calligraphy. I
did like this more readable
>> readable one, [laughter]
not this cool one.
>> Oh, but you haven't used one of those in
a long time.
>> No, I think like I mean the last time I
used it was in elementary school.
>> So, this is one thing if you're
traveling Japan, it's nice to have shoes
that don't have laces you have to tie
up.
>> This is like a nice area.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, I have these plants. I really
like these ones.
>> Yeah. Yeah, these ones are these ones
are
>> I think this is I think this is called
Enu Maki.
>> Enu Maki
>> and I have these at Silver Daisy Hotel.
Silver Daisy stay Niko, please visit.
>> You're promoting promoting your
>> Got to keep on promoting. Always promote
AP. Always be promoting.
>> AP.
>> Stay at one of our three chalets at
Silver Daisy Day Niko. Only a short walk
away from the shrines and temples of
Niko, a UNESCO World Heritage site. Book
today at silverdaistay.com.
AB AB AB pink.
>> What
a
abh
[music]
>> do you love coffee?
>> Uh I actually I actually do recently.
>> You can get your own roast over here.
>> I need to I need to have uh cream inside
though.
>> Weak.
>> Well, you don't you don't drink black
coffee?
>> Yeah, actually I can now.
>> Really? Because I make my own coffee and
then you can make it less bitter.
>> Oh, but I do like a uh I think it's
called am I think it's Americano? I had
>> Oh, that's espresso and water. Hot
water.
>> Yeah, I like that.
>> Really? You drink that black or with
cream?
>> No, I just had it black.
>> Did you drink the Americano in Italy?
>> No, it was in Vancouver, but
>> Okay.
>> I had it with like pastries.
>> So,
>> I don't know. That looks like a really
Japanese bird.
Actually, I don't know. It might be from
a different country.
>> Bird lovers, let us know.
>> It looks cute.
>> These are cherry trees, I'm guessing.
>> So, you can have your hanami here in the
spring.
>> It definitely look way better when it's
warmer.
>> Yeah, I guess so. And once they don't
have that being rebuilt, I swear this is
actually a common scene with all castles
in Japan. They're always in some form of
restoration.
>> Yeah, I think so.
>> Oh, this rock's new rock.
Shaped way too nicely.
>> Oh, yeah. [laughter]
>> That's really thick.
Wow. Wait, it looks pretty like neat to
new.
>> Well, they might have just
restored it. I feel
>> this is all clean.
>> Yeah, I feel like even that one looks
too clean, too. Even though it's done
old style, but it still feels like it's
new.
>> Matas are always cool.
>> I like matzah, which is why I got one
for silver daisy stain
>> again.
>> Yeah, this looks too new.
So this green moss over here, this looks
like original wall.
>> Yeah.
>> And then from here, this is the new
wall.
>> It's newer.
>> I'm sure there wa There's nothing
inside.
>> I don't know if you can tell,
but there's nothing inside at all.
Do you know there's some castles you can
stay in in Japan?
>> Can like You mean like, you know, sleep
inside?
>> Yeah, you can. It's really expensive,
but you can rent it out. Where is that?
>> There's so many castles in Japan.
There's some castle that's doing it, but
I I can't tell you where.
>> Do you think that hotel is um more
expensive than Disney hotel?
>> Castle Hotel is way more expensive. I'll
tell you that.
>> It's like
>> It's really expensive. It's I think it's
a few thousand a night.
>> Thousand
>> like niju sanju.
>> It's It's really expensive. These are
kind of Oh, this see this is sakura.
This look really pretty.
Oh yeah, it would be so cool if the like
the flowers the sakra will be here.
>> Okay, so they're rebuilding to get
inside. It's money.
>> That's that's fine. It's only 320 yen. I
mean, are they really going to rebuild
everything or just part of it?
>> Yeah, because
it's huge.
>> Very huge.
This is what it looked like just a
little while ago, but now it's like this
snowing outside.
>> Yeah. Oh, that looks really That looks
cool. [laughter]
>> Oh, they have the uh muk the what do you
call this?
>> Model.
>> There's a little city. This is where the
governmented
from. [snorts]
Yeah. So, like I said, this castle,
these parts are 2001.
>> 2001. They redid them. We're doing
everything. They all look like this. All
the dant like sit it in this. Yeah.
>> All right. Can you figure out the
puzzle?
>> Oh, so like I guess the middle stick
like keeps it.
>> Okay. We'll put it back together and see
if the middle stick keeps it.
This is Oh, it has a certain
>> Okay, pick it up. Does it actually keep
it?
>> Oh, it does work.
[laughter]
>> It's a double stick.
>> Oh, what? What is this even for? What
>> has like
>> Take it out.
>> But this
>> Ah, okay. Okay. Let's see inside.
Uh,
>> how do people come up with these ideas?
>> Oh, there you go. Take that out, too.
>> Wow. So, if you don't have nails, this
is how you can build without nails.
>> It's like big uh Lego pieces. That's
interesting. Like, yeah, the inside is
like all the strings.
I didn't even see that.
>> There you go.
>> The actual
>> Oh,
>> complicated
>> like the Aver Lavine song. You know the
song?
>> No, I don't.
>> Why you have to make everything so
>> complicated? [music]
>> I know the the boyfriend.
[music]
>> That's too new. That's too new. Here you
go.
>> Oh, that's that's kind of cool.
We visited the castle and it's
completely unheated, right?
>> Yeah. It was really cold inside.
>> Yeah. Even though it was actually
relatively newly built, right? They
restored it over a number of years. And
they're doing like many many parts of
the castle.
>> And they even have displays where you
could see old old style walls and then
like a newer style wall, then like newer
style wall.
>> So, it's kind of interesting if you want
to see how a castle in Japan is built.
>> Yeah. Yeah,
>> they really show you the the behind the
scenes of it.
>> They have like, you know, real the
models of, you know, how many layers it
has on the walls or the rooftop, too.
So, that was pretty cool.
>> Like, so if you're really into castles,
>> you can get to see inside the bones of a
castle.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> But it is newly built, like very But
they used old techniques to build it
new.
It's collecting all the the snow.
>> Winintry mix. Sounds nice.
>> Yeah, I like the sound.
>> There was a fire here at some point.
>> Yeah, but like Yeah, there's the trees
that has like the black
>> too bright. We did go to a newer
building built on the castle grounds was
which was the cafe.
>> Yeah, the cafe. It was like that was
interesting because I don't know if that
was originally a building that was
already there or they just newly built
it. That kind of felt weird. I don't
know like you know just building
something new inside of like a
historical you know place I guess. But I
really like the cafe. So
>> does look good. How's the user? I don't
actually don't really like using like
like the actual parts.
>> I guess it's like little bit of gold
only.
>> Kimaku
soft, I guess.
>> Gold leaf ice cream.
>> Yeah, it's like I mean it's literally
ice cream that has gold flakes.
>> It's very very thin. Like I mean well it
depends which one you get.
>> Yeah.
>> I like yuzu so I got the yuzu version
which has like little thin flakes of the
gold plus yuzu.
>> No
>> I love yuzu is always good. But I found
some Australians there and they ordered
the gold leaf and they were taking their
Instagram pictures. Right.
>> Yeah. I think that was that's the most
common look of it. Like it has like the
whole the whole gold leaf.
>> Yeah. [clears throat] Whole thing on.
But we just only got the little I mean
that was still pretty but
>> Yeah. Yeah. So I borrowed their their
ice cream to take a few pictures like Oh
yeah. Yeah. For sure. Do what you need
to do to take the photos. So they're
really helpful. Thanks a lot.
>> Yeah.
>> Mhm.
>> You recommend
>> for the for the gram.
>> The gram. Yeah.
>> Okay. But FPV mode is first person view.
So anything you look at or do it copies.
>> Oh.
So if you look that way, it goes.
>> Yeah.
>> So drunk mode is like this.
>> Drunk mode.
>> Like see
>> uh
>> drunkness mode.
[snorts]
>> This is like Gen Z style filming.
>> Have you ever been actually drunk?
>> Hey. Hey fam. We're here in
>> How is it Jenzi?
>> What is this castle called? Is it Kano
Castle?
>> Oh, I haven't.
>> Hey fam, we're here at Kazaw Castle.
>> That's who says that you do.
>> I don't not say hey fam.
>> Yeah.
>> [snorts]
>> Oh, they got a little natural
looking
>> kawaii.
>> Uncle Roger would love this.
>> Not too kawaii.
>> What about this one?
>> Uh [snorts] oh. Wow. That's very
aggressive.
>> Aggressive.
>> Oh, I like stuff like this, though.
>> Oh, this is cute.
But don't you think it is kind of too
like
>> uh Well, for this style? Yeah, maybe.
Wow.
>> This actually I mean this I guess maybe
it's cuz it's rainy. It reminds me of
Canada like west coast
>> a little bit. But the plants are really
different. So
>> yeah. Every single place you went to in
the park you had like a really fantastic
view.
>> Mhm.
>> And I saw so many workers there,
>> right?
>> You [laughter] really you're like the
cleaning.
>> Yeah. I filmed a lot of cleaners or or
landscapers or gardeners
>> doing their thing. And you must have a
whole team of people doing that every
single day to maintain this really big
park.
>> Where you going? You're going down the
tally.
>> Okay.
>> Is this is very polite.
>> It's closed though.
>> I like this little I like the little
like this is not alley but you know
little streets.
Whoa, this place looks so Instagrammable
[snorts]
>> or the gram.
>> The gram.
>> One thing I liked about the garden was I
found like no matter where we walked
when we looked out at something because
the elevation was changing because trees
and plants were changing. Each view was
unique and it looked different. So, I
think that's why it's considered a
really great garden is because no matter
where you stand, no matter where you go,
you have a really captivating view.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, look at that. That's the Graham
Bridge.
>> Graham bridge. Uh, I bet like people
sign in the middle.
>> Oh, look at the Graham Bird.
>> Oh,
it came just for us.
>> Yes. Hired. That's so white.
>> Uh,
>> look at the feathers.
>> Cold, you know. Is he shivering or is he
just how he walks? [laughter]
>> It's his swag.
>> Yeah, you know the bird.
>> He's He's riing right now.
>> Rizzing.
>> Yeah.
>> No, that's not.
>> Hey, look. That's his wiz walk.
>> Look, look, look. He's so riing.
>> Wait, I thought I thought he's stepping
on leaves. His foot is actually yellow.
>> Yeah. came in the water and he was like
shivering like [laughter]
>> and every single step he made he was
just looked like he's shivering, right?
>> Yeah.
>> It was super funny, super cute.
>> But I guess we found out he was actually
that's how he finds food inside the
water. Like he shakes his leg, his foot,
and I guess all the little bugs or
whatever comes out and then he eats
them. But we we just thought he was like
so cold. I thought he was doing his
Rizwalk.
>> I called him Rzzy Bird.
>> That's what you call him.
>> He was cool though.
>> Yeah, but he was he was cute.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I think that's the way it's hunched or
something. It all just looks permanently
cool. Gramming again.
>> Mhm.
This is what you wanted. You want the
natural cafe like this? You know, the
one we were in where it's very new.
>> This is traditional style.
>> This is cool. I like this one.
>> But you're not getting there cuz you
already got the new one.
>> Yeah.
>> I like this type of garden. I remember
going into like a the foot onen foot.
>> Ah, yeah. Yeah. That was in
>> there. Doesn't exist anymore, you know.
>> Yeah. It has like the
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, does it hurt your toes?
>> This is probably what it's modeled
after.
>> It's like the actual, right? You know,
the rocks in between.
>> So, this they just need this to be an
onsen.
>> Yeah.
>> Be perfect.
>> This looks like Lord of the Rings type
of trees.
>> Now, I got in the mud of this. Well,
that is cool.
>> Something in the gardens I really liked
were the old trees.
>> Yeah. Even like those I guess parts that
you know society like hold like
>> make shape support the trees. That was
also that also like looked good.
>> Look at this thing. I've never seen a
tree like this.
Cute.
>> It was snowing.
>> Like it was snowing and it like stopped
and it snowed again.
>> Stop, start, stop, start, hail, snow.
>> But that that made it really pretty.
Like
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Very scenic.
>> Yeah. I liked it a lot.
>> If I was a good photographer, I could do
something with this, you know.
>> I think you are good.
I guess photography and like video is a
little different.
>> Yeah. there weren't too much people or
it wasn't crowded or anything. So,
>> we did see a tour bus pull up like and
drop off a whole bunch of people and
then all of a sudden there was just a
massive group of people for a little
bit.
>> Yeah. But before that, it wasn't too
bad.
>> No, not crowd at all.
>> On the way back from the garden
>> going to our hotel or to the market, we
came across a shrine.
>> Yeah. this uh I guess we didn't you
didn't know about the shrine, right?
>> No, I didn't. It looked like a Buddhist
style, but it had like western stained
glass type of
>> feel to it.
>> I I've never seen a shrine with this
type of architecture before. So, that
was just amazing to see. And it is a top
site
>> as we later found out. So, we just
stumbled across it on our way back to
the market.
>> Yeah. So, good luck. Fortune.
>> Fortune on your birthday.
>> My birthday is a secret though.
>> That's long. It's a novel.
>> Oh,
this is my personality
is very
truthful or
I don't know. Oh, I don't um I don't uh
I don't people. Why don't I suddenly
don't know all these words? Oh, so like
I don't suspect people. I don't like
doubt people.
>> So like I believe in them more.
>> Maybe that's I think that's true. Or
maybe I'm just too lazy to think that
they're wrong
>> or that they're on to something. Oh, and
it says I'm a romantic.
>> Romantic.
>> Yeah, I'm a I don't think I'm that much.
Oh, [snorts] and if I So, it says and
all of that. Um, if I'm just living a
normal regular life, then I'll be I'll
I'll be happy.
>> Little old Bubba.
>> Yes.
>> So, there was another place that wasn't
busy, which was Omicho.
>> Omich. And it's called a Ichiba.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, and lots of stuff
around.
>> You might call it like a market or an
arcade.
>> Yeah. It's like kind of close to market.
I think
>> we got there fairly late in the day. I
think around 4:00 p.m.ish.
>> Yeah.
>> And basically all the shops were closed
except for a few restaurants. Like a
very small amount of restaurants.
>> You're too late.
>> Yeah. Cuz I think the peak time is
around I guess lunchtime. So 11 a.m. or,
you know, 12:00 p.m.
>> But I think we should have gone
[laughter] at that time because like
they the shops close fairly early.
>> Yeah.
>> So if you guys [laughter] want to go,
you should go in like in the morning.
So yeah, egg, salmon, and ikura
and Oh, no. No. Yeah. Crab.
>> It's unagi.
>> Yeah. This is your unagi.
>> This looks like ano mita unagi. Tamago.
>> Your egg. And your
>> And you're going to make green tea.
>> And I'll make green tea.
>> This reminds me of the video. One of the
first videos.
>> Really?
>> The kiten sushi one. Kushi.
>> Oh, yeah. making green like this.
[sighs and snorts]
>> Odin, I forgot what she called it. I
don't think it's the usual um ingredient
in
>> Odin. Yeah. I mean like for typical
things. It's very soft. It's really
good.
So like
it's chewy.
>> So like ea kind of texture or no
>> octopus. Taco.
>> Close to taco.
>> Close to octopus.
>> So you've never tried this before?
>> No. It's like b by
>> guy.
>> Yeah. I've only tried like pot or
whatever other things I tried, but it's
very good.
>> Nice. Nice. Nice choice.
>> Kazawen Kazen.
>> And I saw on the wall there was a lot of
um signed
>> I think Shikishi
>> autograph boards.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So I think I guess some
famous people.
>> Yeah. A lot of people must have went to
visit there. And did they get the
signature? They didn't get ours.
>> No.
>> No. [laughter]
It was the kaisen though, the salmon and
the raw fish.
>> After our evening meal, we stopped by a
convenience store to buy makeup remover
for Eeko. And I stumbled upon some new
gummies we hadn't tried. So, of course,
we had to do a
>> tab kurabi tab kurab.
>> Yeah.
>> Kazawa edition.
>> We have [laughter and gasps] the
gumi. So, angel gummies.
But judgement judgement
>> judgment.
>> The yuzu gummies.
>> Yuzu. My favorite
>> citrus fruit.
>> Jelly. Jelly inside.
>> Oh, jelly inside.
>> Fusion.
>> Fusion. Gab.
>> I thought that was blueberries. Let's
Let's put some judgment in.
>> This feels like there's like It might be
jelly jelly. We got double jelly maybe.
Yeah, it is. It is jelly
>> inside.
>> Hot.
>> M. I like this one.
>> And really soft. It is good, actually.
>> Yeah,
>> I like this one.
>> Okay, now we're just going for the yuzu.
Okay.
>> Okay.
It's good, but it's kind of hard. The
battery on our mics died. So, here's a
very accurate reenactment of what we
said. Actually, this is pretty good.
Yeah. Yeah. Better than I thought it
would be. Let's try that Angel Judgment
one again.
Want to eat this one? You do it. You
know what? Angel Judgment is very tasty.
Yeah, it has good flavor and texture. I
like this one. Tenino gummy judgment. If
I only had to choose one, this would be
it. Now, let's go to the record cafe.
>> So, Kame,
>> so there's just this one DJ that's his
whole job is just to like switch back
and forth between the pile of records up
on the wall behind him.
>> Yeah,
>> but you're not supposed to talk to him.
>> Yeah, I think I mean you're not supposed
to like request I guess he wants his
like his music.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Yeah. He probably gets annoyed with
people. Hey, can you play this? Hey, can
you play that? So,
>> no requests.
>> I I like the music choices, too.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. The food was it was really
>> It was really [clears throat] good.
>> So, it was within a hotel, so it it was
more pricey the food
>> than I would say normal, but it was
actually worth the price.
>> I mean, I do like vegetables, but I was
like, "Oh, this."
>> Yeah. It wasn't just like steamed
vegetables. Like, they did it up nicely.
So,
>> it was really tasty. And the dessert.
>> Yeah. The cheesecake was I think it was
like some like unusual
>> Oh, right. Garganzola cheesecake.
>> Yeah. I never [laughter] heard of that.
>> It was good.
>> It was good, though.
>> Yeah. Like I I like cheese, but I would
never think to put garzola cheese into a
cheesecake. So, I thought, oh, but you
know, if they're doing it and it's like
a nicer restaurant, then it's probably
they know how to do it well. And it was
really good.
>> Yeah, it was good.
>> Yeah. The whole place had a really nice
vibe to it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I liked it. The one thing
that surprised me though was the
waitress came with that piece of paper.
Do you remember?
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. She there's this paper
she gave us and it's basically like you
know would you like to tip us?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Never I mean I never seen in Japan
and you know tip tipping culture is not
a thing. So I was like oh
>> I think you can choose like from 100
yen, 300, 500 or something
>> or custom amounts.
>> Yeah. I mean, but the wait wait wait
wait waitress, she was very nice and you
know, she suggested stuff for me. So, I
was like, "Okay." And
>> I mean, I think I only gave her like 300
yen or something.
>> Three or 500 yen. So, a little little
tip, but it's really weird cuz in
Canada, you would actually tip way more
money.
>> Yeah.
>> So, it was kind of just broke my brain a
little bit because just so used to not
tipping, but here they are with like,
"If you like the music, if you liked
everything,
>> how about giving a tip?"
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's weird. I think
there's going to be some people in the
comments like, "No, don't start tipping
culture in Japan." So,
>> I don't I don't want it to start, too.
>> No, no, no. So, the DJ who was playing,
he had the speakers that went out into
the street.
>> So, we didn't go out that late, but it
was there's no people and all the shops
were almost all closed. So, that was
interesting.
>> And you found Gachap? Oh,
>> yeah. Gacha Gacha.
[music]
>> [music]
>> What do you think? What are you getting?
>> The bus stops
>> because you like riding the bus.
>> No, I just like
>> That's your main form of transportation.
The only one you can afford.
>> Yes.
Actually, that's just walking.
>> This is making a really boring video.
>> Uh Uh maybe you can cut
>> this is all the same
>> but it's just
>> it's different color
>> like it's the trend. It's called access.
>> Yeah.
>> So you put these on whatever [music]
whatever you like your phone your
>> car things.
>> Oh look they have all the different
things you can get.
>> Look at this.
this guy on a toilet.
>> Ah, it's okay.
>> I made this seafood salad with shrimps
and I think there's like seaweeds,
purple seaweed, green seaweed,
>> and this one sausage meat.
>> Sure thing. Why not? I don't know. But
it's really good. It has like much cream
inside. And this is a kanazawa curry.
>> Kanazawa curry.
>> Kanazawa curry. Uh, some fruits.
>> Fruits.
>> Healthy.
>> What are you drinking here?
>> Apple juice.
>> I got apple juice. I got very milky
coffee and water.
>> And then I have a kind of zawa curry.
>> Oh, with a tonk.
>> But I put Yeah, I think it comes with
tonkat, I think. But you're supposed to
have it with cabbage. So, I got cabbage
next to my apple pie.
>> I got a sausage next to noto lasagna.
>> This is a local specialty lasagna.
>> Interestingly enough,
>> I got lots of fruits. some grapefruits,
some pineapples, and then I have a
daikon Caesar salad.
>> Daon Caesar salad.
>> Yeah. It doesn't sound like it should be
a thing, but it's daon Caesar salad.
>> Wow.
>> Okay.
>> It was really good. I was surprised
because it's not I mean, the hotel is
good, but it's not like, you know, a
very very uh you know,
>> it's not high-end one.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And you know, usually buffet
styles like it's not like, you know, you
won't really expect a lot. It's just
for, you know, just fun, but it was
really good. And
>> I was surprised that they had a lot of
local dishes. So they had like Kanazawa
curry.
>> Yeah. Know curry.
>> And they had noto lasagna. I didn't know
was famous for lasagna. [laughter]
>> So you got some a lot of local dishes,
not just like the standard. But this
one, everything was I wouldn't say it's
like premium level, but it's like pretty
pretty good.
>> [clears throat]
>> pretty good level.
>> Good morning. It's 8:15 a.m. and I'm
going to pick up a car share rental car.
Usually, I would take public
transportation like a bus or a train,
but there's a specific place that I want
to go to, or more technically, a
specific experience that you can only do
when you have a car. So,
>> we are now about to arrive at Takamatsu
Mitinoi.
>> A miti.
Little smaller than I thought.
>> Smaller than you thought.
>> Okay, let's get some gifts.
>> Yes.
What is this? It looks like licorice but
giant.
>> It's kind of like a candy.
>> Candy. Okay, we should try. We have to
try.
>> And then if they're tasty, we'll buy it
for people. But if it's not tasty, we
won't.
>> Oh, this
curry.
>> Oh, brown butter waffle cookies made in
Japan.
>> Never really seen these. Oh,
>> brown. Is this like the Dutch one, you
know?
>> Uh, like the uh Yeah, the waffles.
Was it stro? No. No.
>> I forgot the name, but I know what
you're talking about.
>> Stroke waffles. [snorts]
>> Hey, is this for Akobachan?
>> Ki. Does she like kisbe?
>> Maybe. I don't know. I do not like
kisbe.
>> It sounds good though.
It has the golden
ginger
ginger.
>> I think I want to try that because I
really love ginger ale. It's from
Kazala.
>> Is this like copyright? No. No. Or
something.
>> It's got to be official. Japan. Oh,
>> no. I mean like
>> That's a cool tin though. Oh,
>> right. That's kind of cute.
>> Oh, that's cute.
>> All right. What are we trying first? Uh,
we're getting trying the
Sahama. I think this is sweet, but I
never heard of.
>> Open it up.
>> Yeah.
>> I just noticed this little cat logo is
really cute.
>> That looks like kind of uh
Yamato.
>> The stolen. The forbidden Yamato. You
got to get a closer. Give it Give it a
closer look.
>> My hands are dry, so you can do it.
>> Leave it for your nails. There we go.
Kinaco.
>> Yeah. I mean, I don't I like kinakle
flavor, but I just don't know about like
the texture. Like, what is this?
>> The texture is really interesting. I
like the texture.
>> Really?
>> Just feels like they put sugar on some
kinako, but then they glued it together.
>> Yeah. I wouldn't get this for people.
Sorry.
>> It's a pass. I think just this because
like it's just funny. It I mean it's
only two. It's not like a big pack.
>> Well, I'll give it to someone, but I'm
not going to eat that.
>> Yeah,
>> I'm not going to get a mega pack.
>> Like maybe like once and you're like,
"Yeah, that was fun to try."
>> Very interesting.
>> In Japanese like
don't they? That's not usually
>> that's not a good thing compliment
[laughter]
>> in Japanese you say like
that's
>> be polite that's like the worst thing
you could say though cuz they don't say
like oh maz I mean unless it's it has to
be horrible to say but
[laughter]
>> okay I'm going to see if I can get this
opened
>> I got this opened
>> craft So that's why I went to get it. So
>> I don't like gingery ginger.
>> Oh, well taste it.
>> It Well, you go first. It's your drink.
>> Okay.
[snorts]
It doesn't have that kick. I think like
>> you feel like it's going to kick in.
>> I'm like [clears throat] that happens a
lot with like
>> really strong ginger bear,
>> but it doesn't come.
[laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah, it doesn't come.
>> But you thought it was going to come,
right?
>> There was a funny uh
>> Huh. It's like you feel like it's going
to go but it just fades away.
>> Unfortunately, [laughter]
I don't think I can recommend this to my
brothers as well. They want something
with more kick,
>> I think. Yeah. Yeah. If you're like
imagining something strong, but no, it's
good for me because I'm not really good
with a fizzy pop.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I like it.
>> Great for you. I feel like we're 0 for
I'm 0 for two on this.
>> But I'm glad I didn't buy a whole bunch.
I just tried it out.
>> It's interesting.
>> We're back again cuz Aiko wants to taste
that. I will pass from tasting it.
>> What? Uh
[snorts] like [laughter]
Okay, I got to try this. This is worse
than the other one? No, I was like I
mean I think because I never had a
grease so I don't really know what the
flavor is.
>> This is worse. This is worse.
>> Do you see the grape over there with
eyes?
>> We got to go sit in there. Sit in it.
>> What is That's not a grape with eyes.
>> It looks like a grape with eyes. Is it
getting better? Mm-m. Second. Okay.
Bye-bye.
>> Yeah. Why would it be a grape? Maybe
this is the purple tree.
>> You should make it the king or whatever
cuz I don't have an image of grape for
>> Okay, let's read the sign.
>> This is
See,
>> so just grape house. I mean,
>> you're supposed to sit there and
>> we should have done the eating
>> eating out.
>> That's so cute.
>> It's wet.
>> Yeah.
>> Uhoh.
>> Okay, I won't do that.
>> Oh, it's hard to see cuz it's yellow.
>> Now I'm cold. My my pants are wet. That
was fun.
>> Okay, let's go. Oh, wait. This is
garbage, isn't it? Look.
>> Wow. What they don't want you to see.
>> Yeah, that's uh Wow.
>> That's incredible amount of garbage.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's Oh, but there are
some rocks. I thought like those are all
But
>> I mean, it pretty much is all Are you
sure it's rocks or styrofoam? So many uh
pet bottles.
>> So this is the Sea of Japan. And so you
don't know where all this garbage is
coming from.
>> That's Whoa. And it just just keeps on
>> like a garbage field. I'm surprised they
at least don't clean it up near here.
>> Yeah, cuz you can like see it from the
>> cuz this is a tourist stop. I wasn't
going to try the ashiu, but they don't
have it. Um, but I don't know if I want
to stick my skin into that.
>> Oh, cuz we were trying to go
and it just says on there.
>> Oh, okay. So, maybe we'll just see the
>> the sign. Maybe I don't know if there's
another entrance that we can go on.
>> Well, we'll check it out. So, this would
be normally how we get on.
>> That's sad. I was like I've seen the
sign like we can't go on Nugget the
driveways but I was like oh yeah we
don't doesn't matter but that's
>> there might be there might be another
entrance where we could but it could be
the time of year it could be the the
weather.
>> Yeah. I mean it was kind of windy and
like I think the waves are really close
to the um beach like the sand.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. Here we go.
>> Oh
>> because of waves
>> they've already Yeah.
>> Wo. Look at all this garbage.
>> Wo.
>> Wo. Yeah. You definitely cannot drive.
Oh, we're we're doing kind of the drive
>> just from the side.
>> Let's open the window and get some
sounds. The sounds of the sea.
>> We're doing as close as we can.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah, that' be definitely be dangerous
to drive along there.
>> I mean, here there's snow like space.
>> Wa.
The waves were too close to the shore.
So, I mean, the car just couldn't
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, your car would get
swept away into the ocean.
>> Yeah. So, there's not enough, you know,
sand area, so we [laughter] couldn't
>> So, something about the beach that
really surprised me was all the garbage
that came up from the ocean.
>> Yeah. There was a all these like pet
bottles and just random garbage. just
anything really.
>> Yeah,
>> they're from all sorts of countries.
Like there's lots of stuff from Japan. I
read stuff in like Korean. I read stuff
in Chinese.
>> So it was a whole mix of stuff that's
just flowing from the ocean cuz this is
the the Sea of Japan.
>> Yeah.
>> So I guess ocean currents just pushed
them in.
>> Yeah. I mean it was incredible the
amount of garbage there. I I was quite
surprised.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
>> All right.
Here we go. So,
look, there's an alien apologizing to
us, though.
[snorts]
>> Yeah.
>> It's under Can you read the English part
of this?
>> Driver is close traffic under the
influence of waves.
>> Under the influence of waves. It's like
it's drunk with waves.
>> Oh,
>> under the influence.
>> Influence of waves
>> means like you you've drunk alcohol.
You're under the influence.
The aliens like
he's come again.
>> He's nice though. He's nice.
[music]
>> Look, I found out there's mala gerato.
>> Oh,
>> so give it the money.
>> What? What is this?
>> My wallet. So buy a daboo, please. Capu.
>> Okay.
>> You have to put the money in, Michael.
>> Oh,
>> don't you know how this works?
>> No. Yeah.
>> I thought you press it.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> It wants the money first.
>> Then you can press the cup. All right.
>> Wa.
She's not shy. [laughter]
>> That's a big portion size, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Wo.
>> That's nice. Oh, the colors look the
same.
>> Wow.
>> Whoa.
>> They got more kinds.
>> New patch.
>> She's giving us a Oh, a free scoop.
>> So, let's try.
>> I actually wanted to try the mascot.
Okay. Well, there you go.
>> You like it?
>> Okay. Now, I'm going to try the yuzu.
I'm already on to the next one.
>> Are you still You got to comment
comment.
>> No. No. It tastes like nostalgic. Like I
think I had a drink or something like
this when I was young. That's the yuzu.
Like there's like the aftertaste and it
has yuzu.
>> Yeah. But it doesn't hit you right away.
>> I feel like the the like the pear is
like it's stronger. No. I I actually
like this.
>> I feel like the shio is going to be my
favorite
>> cuz I don't usually honestly I don't get
citrus with ice cream. I find I'm not a
big fan.
>> But I like berries like strawberry,
blueberry.
>> Yeah.
Oh, this is Oh, this actually good.
Tastes just close to a like, you know,
[music] regular vanilla standard. Yeah.
But I mean, you can taste the salty.
>> Oh, this is good. Yeah. I don't really
like salt ice cream. That sounds
>> really salty ice cream's good. Salty
caramel ice cream.
>> Oh, well, okay. That is good. But like
just salt ice cream. That sounds not
really. But no, this is good. M.
>> Yeah. I think I like the salt ice cream
the rest.
>> These chips actually look tasty.
>> Yeah, these chips.
>> Do you want to try a chips then?
>> Yeah. Mitsu.
>> Okay. Which you going to pick? The one
with GMA or with
>> Oh, there's different flavors. Um,
>> tan.
>> Well, this is coated with like mitsu, so
sweet syrup. But I think I do like the
purple ones.
>> Okay. Well, then let's get the mix mixed
up.
>> Slightly expensive though. No,
>> we got to do it for the
>> for the YouTube.
>> We can't do the ground for the YT.
>> For the YT.
>> For the youth.
>> For the YT. Okay.
>> Yeah. See, they have really good
artwork.
>> Is this because lots of trucks and cars
are purple here?
>> Yes, it is.
>> Because of this.
>> Oh, you're asking why you saw them on
the road?
>> Yeah, because I saw like two or three
purple trucks and one purple car. Like I
never seen
>> This is what I wanted to do. I wanted to
go on the beach and then Because usually
it's like all open like this. But today
was like
>> the thing was
>> there was no beach. It was just always
>> of course we have the Kimpaku.
>> Oh, this is the Kanazawa gold.
>> Mhm.
>> Wow.
Amazing.
Look, you can get the
>> Oh, cute.
>> The gold mask.
>> Moist mask.
>> Oh, we have the
>> Oh, no. The megaized ones.
No, no, no, no, no,
>> noation.
>> There's just too much to film.
>> Um, it's I guess alien.
>> That is that why they have the alien on
the sign?
>> I don't know what's with the aliens.
>> Aliens come here.
>> That That is uh That is
>> This looks like the artwork we saw last
night.
>> Last night?
>> Yeah. Those legs that were running. Oh.
Yeah. The leg thing. This was a thing
that was in the Odin yesterday. [music]
>> Okay. So, it's just bread.
>> I cannot read this, but you know. We
>> kugi. Yeah.
>> Which one do you want to be?
>> Looking good. Looking good.
Wa. Let's Oh, check out the sand. Sand
sculpture.
>> Sand.
>> Wow. This reminds me of Mon noahime.
>> This is like dragon eating the sushi.
>> Okay, let's go.
>> Feel like the kang is cold now. Yeah,
this is like really a
what is it? Jenzie Tik Tok style.
>> Oh yeah, that's what we're all about
here.
>> Curry bread. H
>> wild boar. Oh. Oh, that's a salty
>> salt from Noto
potato chips.
>> Yeah, but these are made of satsumo.
>> Satsumo.
>> Crunchy.
>> Mhm. [clears throat]
>> Good.
>> Nice.
>> Mine's still no flavor. It's very very
like plain bun. Yeah.
Kind of a cut or something.
the one that I had this morning.
Oh
>> Now I got the hit of salt. I like the
salt.
>> I think they should spread the salt
throughout cuz it's only one bite. You
get all the salt and then
>> Oh, really?
>> There's no other like Yeah.
>> I've been very negative this morning
about my food so far.
>> Man, usually you're pretty happy.
>> Like pear taste.
>> It doesn't taste like salt. So
>> it's just bread. Exactly. So I'm
expecting something. It's good, but I
mean it just spreads.
>> This is good.
>> Yeah, I don't even like curry that much,
but this is good. Yeah,
>> this one's good.
>> There you go. I'm positive about
something.
>> So, I'll get the the yellow one.
>> I thought you like the purple ones.
>> I like the purple ones.
>> Show it. Show it close. They can't even
see it. Closer.
>> Well, my h my hands are so dry. And
>> here, hide your face. Oh, there you go.
Here. Closer. And you can see my dry
hands. I don't want that.
>> Whoa.
That's very
>> crunchy.
>> That's good.
>> M. Mhm. I think I poked myself with the
chips.
>> What?
>> I poked myself inside the mouth.
>> Oh no. You cut your mouth. Eat that.
>> You
>> [singing]
>> Hi co. Do you think these are like
Canadian geese where they're dangerous?
>> Uh they these guys Yeah. sometimes tend
to be
dangerous.
>> What are they doing in the rice fields?
>> No, they're making the rice.
>> Oh, that's how they workers. Yes.
>> Okay. Okay. I'm going to go and get a
closer up look.
>> Uh-oh.
They're talking about us. They
definitely are saying like,
>> "Look, he's coming. He's coming."
>> I guess they're not like Canadian geese.
Canadian geese wouldn't walk away from
you.
>> They do not like us. They're going away.
Someone left. [laughter]
>> They're The sound they make is so
interesting.
>> Yeah, they sound like they're panicking
now.
They weren't this loud because it's
because we came.
>> Yeah, [laughter]
>> they're all going in the line that way.
So cute.
[music]
[singing]
>> It looks so tiny bit though.
>> Arts shrinkflation. So like mine's a
really thick thick broth.
>> Would totally like this. Like I think
it's
>> okay. Is it Is it fishy?
>> It's fishy fish.
>> Yeah. I got mine very light. I'm going
to try your broth.
>> Wow. It's very fishy. Totally not my not
my vibe.
>> Yeah. Do you like fishy?
>> Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow,
>> it's really good.
[singing and music]
>> Welcome to Notojima.
Like announcer announcement.
It's a kind of fancy
>> tot.
Well, you
>> I'm surprised you read that. I I They
looked like just lines to me.
>> I read the English one.
>> Oh, it is English.
>> It is English.
>> Oh, no. Actually, it said
[singing and music]
>> this place looks abandoned.
>> I haven't been to one for so long, but I
like the first part. It was really um
like flashy. [laughter]
>> That's where they spent their money.
>> It's very
good.
>> Hey fam,
>> why do you look You look short.
>> We at the aquarium, fam.
>> No. [music]
Is this our style today? A good style?
Oh,
>> welcome to the sea of Noto.
>> How do you I don't know how to flip the
camera.
>> What? You press the button.
>> Oh.
>> Wow. Oh, is that
>> I think they're going in a big circle.
>> Oh, the floor is very
This is very
>> Let's see.
It's very uh confusing.
So many fishes. Whoa. Chicken grunt.
>> Yeah. And the spangled emperor.
>> That's an awesome name.
>> Oh no. Oh, I thought they're dead.
>> You're blocking my view.
>> This dude's crying. Oh no.
>> Oh.
>> Oh. This is kind of
Oh. Oh, they're flying right over our
heads. That's cool.
>> Wo.
Oh, hi.
So, [music] it's like,
[laughter]
look at this dude.
>> Oh,
>> he's showing off his big mouth.
>> Big guy over there.
>> The guy in the back, he's just hiding.
[music] He's creeping.
>> That guy looks like a shark.
>> This guy is a shark. Don't sing the
song. [clears throat]
>> He's doing a little wiggle.
>> Oh, little guy came.
[laughter]
>> Here's a more
smaller
slower fishes.
>> The smaller slower fish get stuck here.
[laughter]
The forgotten fish.
>> Oh, you can touch these.
>> I don't want to touch. I don't want to
touch.
>> This is what I ate. This is what I ate
yesterday.
>> You ate him?
>> Yeah.
in the yesterday. Very good. It's like
this like free food. That's what you you
eat that too.
>> Oh, the shin shinoi.
>> Oh,
>> he made a very uh
>> gajin. Sorry. Sorry for being gajun.
>> Oh, look at they're really want to look.
They're going crazy. [laughter]
>> They're going crazy. They want to eat
your hand.
>> Don't do it.
It feels like someone's kissing my hand.
Oh my god.
>> Just put it in already. Like put it
deep.
>> I can't.
>> And you got to see.
>> Do it for the ground.
>> Do it.
>> They love it.
>> Oh, they're just so excited.
>> It's like a like a massage.
[laughter]
It feels so beautiful.
>> You have to pay so much money for this.
>> Yeah. Oh my god. You should try.
>> I've done it with my feet before. Yeah,
they're with my feet. But this these
guys are so aggressive.
>> They know.
>> How about these guys? These guys,
>> they're all the same.
>> I mean, yeah, but like these guys wants
some, too. Maybe.
>> Some guys are actually like climbing up.
>> Does my hand actually get cleaned by
this?
>> I don't know. Maybe I can. Oh, you can't
pick them up though. Taco.
It's the um biggest biggest octopus in
the world. I guess
>> this one it looks really small for the
biggest octopus.
>> Yeah.
>> The variety is the biggest. You mean
>> I Well, I don't know. I think it says
like 2 m. They're 20 kilog.
>> These are yummy suction cups.
>> Do you like those?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, I mean he Oh, ew. [laughter]
What's wrong with his
>> Yeah. Yeah. What is that?
>> Yeah. What is that in him?
>> Oh, what is that?
>> That That doesn't look normal.
>> Is that a
>> Why? What is that? Is a ball inside of
him.
>> It's like a human bone sticking out or
something.
>> He ate a human.
>> I don't know. This guy is Maybe that's
why he's alone.
>> Oh, it was bubbles.
>> Oh,
>> but they're really ugly. Finally got the
cute cute fish. Oh,
>> clown anam fish.
>> Shot this guy. Um, pooping. Yeah, these
guys are small and cute.
>> These guys looked very dangerous.
>> Dangerous. Oh,
>> you get stuck in that. The
>> ones that Nemo Nemo got stuck on.
They're
>> in the ceiling, dude.
Oh. Oh, yeah. They're in the ceiling.
>> That's a little freaky. We didn't know
that.
>> Wait, are these turtles?
>> Yeah, they're sea turtles, are they not?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> Didn't you watch Planning Nemo?
>> Oh.
>> Oh, and these are the [laughter]
a smaller guys.
>> They really look like they're flying in
water, right? Yeah.
>> Flop flap flap.
>> They look funny. These guys are These
guys are cute.
>> Oh, I think that's their voice. I
thought that was a person's voice.
>> Yeah, that's what I thought, too.
>> What do you think these boats fish for?
M I mean I don't know what fish.
[laughter]
>> Really? You have no clue then?
>> No, I don't have any clue about fish.
>> I don't know either. I have no clue.
>> So after the aquarium, where did we go?
>> To another um Ichiba. So we're trying to
like do revenge.
>> Yeah.
>> But we also got there
>> around I think Yeah. Yeah. around 4 or
5. So it was like most of the shops
>> I'd say like 80% was closed.
>> Yeah.
>> So that's probably another experience
where Yeah. you want to go a bit earlier
>> than an hour before they closed.
>> Yeah.
>> Nice.
>> Oh, this is where I saw the piano.
>> Oh, right.
>> Oh, and there's Hanu.
So, I don't know.
Look how pixelated it is.
>> Oh, shiny [laughter] notice.
>> Cool layout.
>> Oh, yeah. That's a cool layout. [music]
>> But does this guy look funny to you?
>> Uh,
[music] no.
>> No, he's totally normal.
>> He's But they all have the same face.
>> He looks a bit constipated, honestly.
Especially [snorts] this guy.
>> Strong taste.
>> Oh,
>> okay. Ice cream is melting. So, let's
have ice cream first. Okay.
>> I like that.
>> M. Oh, that's very um thick. M.
>> Right. Hokkaido soft ice cream at
Costco.
>> Yeah. Yeah,
it kind of does.
>> I like this type.
>> What about
Okay, let's try it out.
>> M.
Sorry. That's squid.
>> That's what it looks like inside.
>> What?
>> The outside is squid.
>> Oh, okay. M the inside is um rice.
>> Noi.
>> Oh, okay. Okay, now I understand. I was
like, that's just what what I was so
confused.
>> Squid on the outside, rice on the
inside.
>> On the inside.
>> Okay. Show the rice on the inside.
>> What do you think?
>> M. It was good. It tastes like um
like the sticky rice
>> in like some u like when you get Chinese
food.
>> Yeah.
>> It's kind of like that.
>> Oh, okay. Okay.
>> But with
>> what overall did you think about
Kanazawa or about the trip?
>> I mean I I liked it. I enjoyed it a lot
and it was like because I never went
really went on that side of Japan.
>> And you know I didn't really everybody
got to eat like you know you know like
fresh seafood. So that was really good.
And I mean, I felt like it would have
been better if I went in maybe like more
spring or summertime just because, you
know, the garden
>> I mean, the garden looked really pretty,
but maybe it would be more like green
>> and it it would just look better. But I
I enjoyed it a lot.
>> I mean, there's so many things to do
that you can easily spend a couple days
there with no problem.
>> Um, and you don't you can get around
quite easily without a car. And there's
a couple places we didn't visit like the
Samurai area or Kimono area. And we
didn't make a side trip to Toyama. That
was the other prefixure. And I actually
really want to go to Toyama. So sorry
about Toyama. I really want to go.
There's is it Shirakawo?
>> Yeah.
>> Instead of going there, we went to Noto.
But I think at this time of year going
to Shirakawo maybe they had some snow
there would have been really scenic. So
it might have been the better choice.
Uh, but I want to try to keep everything
into the same prefecture. So,
>> and I went to visit Noto because they
had the, you know, recent earthquake and
tsunami. So,
>> went over there instead.
>> But yeah, I'd really recommend going to
Kanazawa. It's a really quick trip from
Tokyo. Yeah, I just had a lot of, you
know, fun on the trip. It was learned a
lot of stuff and it was cool to hang out
with you.
>> Yeah. You don't usually
>> we're not we're not friends.
[laughter]
Well, yeah. No, we're father and
daughter. We're father and daughter.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But it was a fatherdaughter
trip. That was nice.
>> Thanks for watching. See you next time.
Bye
>> bye. What's a historical town like where
you're from?
Peace.
[laughter]
>> Okay. Can you name them all?
>> To
this.
I mean that's
I think that was a shishi look.
>> Okay. Yeah.
>> There's a man
and Whoa. What is that?
>> You knowishi around the neck.
>> Oh, okay. And then
>> and that's
Oh, and that's a that's buckas
likes